Hey everyone! So today I'm on my way to Dortmund and I'm going to have a photoshoot there with a friend of mine,
who is also a very talented photographer, makeup artist, Diana.
So yeah, I got up and had breakfast and my makeup
Now driving there. I think we'll shoot two sets one latex and one other katsuit
I took a lot of time doing my makeup today because it doesn't only have to hold up for the shoot
But I'm also going to party tonight
But yeah, for the shooting part at least I will take you with me
Enjoy!
I'm weighing up my options
I guess I'll never know
I'll show you every weakness
I'll show you every flaw
Just promise you won't leave here
Just promise there is more
How bad is my luck
When the fragments scar your hands
Of my broken heart
It's clear
My heart is glass
I know the days still pass
And the world still spins round
I know the rain won't last
And the sun still goes down
But my heart is glass
And it's tumbling to the ground
Without you
It breaks
My heart is glass
Will you
Will you think about me
The way I thought of you
There's blood on the floor
Shattered pieces in your hands
You walk through the door
And leave
My heart is glass
Will you, will you think about me
The way I thought of you
Will you think about me?
My heart is glass
The way I thought of you
Will you think about me?
My heart is glass
Have a look here, you can see that the lathe was tight.